<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<library xmlns="http://www.demandware.com/xml/impex/library/2006-10-31">
    <folder folder-id="root">
        <online-flag>true</online-flag>
        <page-attributes />
    </folder>
    <content content-id="faqContent">
        <display-name xml:lang="x-default">Faq content</display-name>
        <display-name xml:lang="en">Faq content</display-name>
        <online-flag>true</online-flag>
        <searchable-flag>false</searchable-flag>
        <page-attributes />
        <custom-attributes>
            <custom-attribute attribute-id="body" xml:lang="x-default">Q. How can I cancel my
                order?&#13;
                A. You can cancel your order before it is shipped by logging in to your My Account
                section. In case, you wish to cancel your order after it is shipped, please contact
                our customer care number-9599227343 or through live chat or email with your order
                details to our customer care email id- customercare.tbs@questretail.in to assist
                you. In case of cancellation of prepaid orders, a refund of any amount paid will be
                processed to the source of payment, within 7-10 business days as per our Exchange
                Return policies.&#13;
                &#13;
                Q. Can i change my order online after i have put it through, to order a different
                size?&#13;
                A. Once the order is confirmed, then you cannot amend the order, however, please
                contact our customer care number-9599227343 or through live chat or email with your
                order details our customer care email id- customercare.tbs@questretail.in for
                further assistance.&#13;
                &#13;
                Q. How do i make changes to my order?&#13;
                A. Once the order is confirmed, then you cannot amend the order, however, please
                contact our customer care number-9599227343 or through live chat or email with your
                order details our customer care email id- customercare.tbs@questretail.in for
                further assistance.&#13;
                &#13;
                Q. What Are The Available Payment Options? &#13;
                A. The following payment methods are available for you to make payment: Cash on
                Delivery (COD)/ Credit/Debit card/ Net Banking/ Unified Payment Interface (UPI)/
                Wallet/ Gift Card. www.thebodyshop.in is set up to take immediate orders accepts
                online through the payments via domestic credit cards issued by Banks and
                Institutions that are part of Visa /Master card. It also accepts Visa / Mestro Debit
                Cards issued by Indian Banks and Amex Cards or Net banking payment mode of selected
                banks of India. For select banks in India – a full list is available at the time of
                check out and prior to making the payment for purchase. You may also make payment
                via Cash on Delivery (COD) at the time of the delivery of the product. However this
                mode of payment facility is only available in selected region / area as specified by
                the Body Shop India. Hence, based on your location and your choice of products, COD
                option may or may not be available to you.&#13;
                &#13;
                Q. Are my credit or debit card details saved?&#13;
                A. We have gone to great lengths to make your shopping experience safe and secure.
                You can use your credit/debit cards without any worries; we have processes in place
                to keep the customer data safe and secure.&#13;
                &#13;
                Q. Can i change my payment details once my order has been submitted?&#13;
                A. Once the order is confirmed, then you cannot amend the order, however, please
                contact our customer care number-9599227343 or through live chat or email with your
                order details our customer care email id- customercare.tbs@questretail.in for
                further assistance.&#13;
                &#13;
                Q. How can i change my password?&#13;
                A. You can log in to your account at any time and amend your password. If you are on
                mobile, head to the Settings tab by clicking on the menu icon on the top left-hand
                corner of your screen. When the settings menu pops up, click on the Update Password
                option. On the desktop, click the My Account icon on the top right-hand side of your
                screen. Once signed in, click on the Settings tab and navigate to the Update
                Password option. This is the page you need! You'll be prompted to enter your
                existing password and choose a new password. Once you have chosen and entered your
                new password, you will get a confirmation message and you are done!</custom-attribute>
        </custom-attributes>
    </content>
    <content content-id="faqContent2">
        <online-flag>true</online-flag>
        <searchable-flag>false</searchable-flag>
        <custom-attributes>
            <custom-attribute attribute-id="body" xml:lang="x-default">Q.What if an item is out of
                stock?&#13;A.Explain how you handle out-of-stock items, including whether customers
                can backorder items or sign up to be notified when they are back in
                stock.&#13;Q.What if I have a problem with my order?&#13;A.Encourage customers to
                reach out to your customer support team if they encounter any issues with their
                orders and assure them that you are committed to resolving any problems
                promptly.&#13;Q.Do you ship internationally?&#13;A.Clarify whether you offer
                international shipping and provide information on additional costs, customs duties,
                and estimated delivery times for international orders.&#13;Q.Do you offer discounts
                or promotions?&#13;A.Inform customers about any ongoing promotions, discounts for
                first-time buyers, referral programs, or loyalty rewards they can take advantage
                of.&#13;Q.What is your shipping policy?&#13;A.Explain your shipping rates, estimated
                delivery times, and any specific shipping policies such as free shipping thresholds
                or international shipping options.</custom-attribute>
        </custom-attributes>
        <folder-links>
        </folder-links>
    </content>

</library>